DUVAN MATEO DUQUE URREA

SENIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

+6 years of experience as a Software Developer. High sense of belonging, good dynamism and personal improvement aspirations, team work ability. Passionate problem solver, keep up with the latest technologies and development methods, constantly expanding my skills as a self-taught learner. Javascript lover and its entire ecosystem. I've worked with NodeJS, React, Angular and C#. Ability to analyze and face challenges that seek improvement through IT solutions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer at Imagemaker

October 2022 - Present · [Medellín, Colombia]

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Develop and migrate new functionalities for the Santander Bank website using best practices and development standards with technologies such as: Angular, Typescript, Node, Scrum, DevOps, Unit Test.
- Create micro frontends for new implementations

Frontend Developer at I.A.S Ingeniería, Aplicaciones y Software S.A.S

March 2021 - Sept 2022 · 1 year 7 months [Medellín, Colombia]

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Developed web applications using React and AWS.
- Design and development of the frontend part of the module that allows the creation of reports on a large number of topics related to the perception and use of artificial intelligence.
- Developed a website for the consultation and optimization of customer search that the Bank has.

Software Developer at JUJU

March 2019 - March 2021 · 2 yrs [Medellín, Colombia]

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Developed and designed new features for the shopping cart.
- Creation and update of stored procedures.
- Improve the behavior and speed of the shopping cart.

Software Developer at 1Cero1 Software

January 2018 - March 2019 · 1 year 3 months [Medellín, Colombia]

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Creation of web portals with payment gateway (PSE) for the mayors of Colombia.
- Communication and management with the different clients of the municipalities.
- Supported and improved legacy modules.

SKILLS

- Problem solving
- Team player
- Fast learner
- Agile principles
- RxJS
- Jest

- Database administration.
- Web Development (SPA)
- Mentoring
- Active listening

- Git
- NodeJS
- JavaScript
- React
- NextJS
- Angular

EDUCATION

Software Developer at CESDE

March 2018 - [Medellín, Colombia]

LANGUAGES

Spanish and English.